import { Exercise } from ".";

export const ITEMS: Exercise[] = [
  {
    "question": "телефон",
    "answer": "tielefon",
    "extra": "📱"
  },
  {
    "question": "книга",
    "answer": "kniga",
    "extra": "📚"
  },
  {
    "question": "часы",
    "answer": "czasy",
    "extra": "⌚"
  },
  {
    "question": "ключ",
    "answer": "kliucz",
    "extra": "🔑"
  },
  {
    "question": "сумка",
    "answer": "sumka",
    "extra": "👜"
  },
  {
    "question": "яблоко",
    "answer": "jabłoko",
    "extra": "🍎"
  },
  {
    "question": "письмо",
    "answer": "pis´mo",
    "extra": "✉️"
  },
  {
    "question": "карандаш",
    "answer": "karandasz",
    "extra": "✏️"
  },
  {
    "question": "очки",
    "answer": "oczki",
    "extra": "👓"
  },
  {
    "question": "зонтик",
    "answer": "zontik",
    "extra": "☔"
  },
  {
    "question": "звезда",
    "answer": "zwiezda",
    "extra": "⭐"
  },
  {
    "question": "сердце",
    "answer": "sierdce",
    "extra": "❤️"
  },
  {
    "question": "луна",
    "answer": "łuna",
    "extra": "🌙"
  },
  {
    "question": "цветок",
    "answer": "cwietok",
    "extra": "🌸"
  }
];
